{
    "subject": "Irving_Thalberg",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Norma_Shearer",
    "human_readable": "Irving Thalberg is married to Norma Shearer.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.988577127456665,
            "question": "Is Norma Shearer married to Irving Thalberg?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9826558828353882,
            "question": "Is there a marriage connection mentioned between Irving Thalberg and Norma Shearer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9367112517356873,
            "question": "To whom was Irving Thalberg married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.936171293258667,
            "question": "Who is Irving Thalberg married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9260203242301941,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Irving Thalberg and Norma Shearer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9025418758392334,
            "question": "Name the spouse of Irving Thalberg."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7724553346633911,
            "question": "What is the name of Irving Thalberg's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6426483988761902,
            "question": "Who is Norma Shearer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15555483102798462,
            "question": "Which person is married to whom according to this information?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09612541645765305,
            "question": "Identify the individuals involved in a marriage relationship described in this statement."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Irving Thalberg is married to Norma Shearer.",
            "html": "yago_2678_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which person is married to whom according to this information?",
            "html": "yago_2678_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Norma Shearer?",
            "html": "yago_2678_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Irving Thalberg's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_2678_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2678_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2678_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2678_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2678_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2678_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2678_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2678_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2678_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2678_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_2678_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents confirm that Norma Shearer was indeed married to Irving Thalberg. This information can be found in several files, including file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_2678/re-ranker-msmarco/4.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_2678/re-ranker-msmarco/83.txt."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide clear information that supports the statement \"Irving Thalberg is married to Norma Shearer.\" Multiple sources indicate their marriage in 1927, further confirming this relationship."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}